If the job doesn't kill you, retirement will.
Polar is a action, crime, drama film directed by Jonas Åkerlund.
When a retiring assassin realizes that he is the target of a hit, he winds up back in
the game going head to head with a gang of younger, ruthless killers.
Duncan Vizla, played by Mads Mikkelsen.
Camille, played by Vanessa Hudgens.
Vivian, played by Katheryn Winnick.
Regina, played by Inga Cadranel.
Hilde, played by Fei Ren.
Sindy, played by Ruby O. Fee.
Polar is a 2019 neo-noir action thriller film directed by Jonas Åkerlund and written by Jayson
Rothwell, based on Víctor Santos's 2013 graphic novel Polar: Came From the Cold.
The film stars Mads Mikkelsen, Vanessa Hudgens,
Katheryn Winnick, and Matt Lucas.
It revolves around an aging assassin on the verge of retirement who becomes
targeted by his employer wanting to cash in on his pension.
Polar was released worldwide on Netflix on January 25, 2019.
A second film, The Black Kaiser, is in development.
The film explores themes of assassin, hitman,
montana, chile, based on graphic novel.
The tone is dark and emotional.